<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevLog: Nilrem and the Hourglass of Time on Jeff Kwak&#39;s Web Log</title>
    <link>https://jeffkwak.com/series/devlog-nilrem-and-the-hourglass-of-time/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevLog: Nilrem and the Hourglass of Time on Jeff Kwak&#39;s Web Log</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 07:59:07 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jeffkwak.com/series/devlog-nilrem-and-the-hourglass-of-time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brackeys Game Jam 2020.2 Day 3</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwak.com/posts/brackeys-game-jam-2020-2-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 07:59:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwak.com/posts/brackeys-game-jam-2020-2-day-3/</guid>
      <description>2020-08-03 0759H EDT Today working on a lot of the generation algorithms. Primary dungeon and path generation will be complete today. Need to get as far as the REWIND mechanic.
2020-08-03 0847H EDT Have initial room spawning complete. Need to get some work done at the office (remotely of course).
2020-08-03 2016H EDT Actually not spawning Nilrem in the GameController. Nilrem and the first room always spawn at the same location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brackeys Game Jam 2020.2 Day 2</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwak.com/posts/brackeys-game-jam-2020-2-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:03:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwak.com/posts/brackeys-game-jam-2020-2-day-2/</guid>
      <description>2020-08-02 1005H EDT I think I&amp;rsquo;m actually going to spend the time to put together a skeleton and some stories. I&amp;rsquo;d like to get a rough idea of the size of this project. I have a suspicion that it&amp;rsquo;s too big.
2020-08-02 1135H EDT I built out a rough backlog, which made me make a couple of decisions.
 I decided to use the URP template in Unity because it&amp;rsquo;s the easiest to use and I wanted to add a little juice with Shader and the Effects Graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brackeys Game Jam 2020.2 Day 1</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwak.com/posts/brackeys-game-jam-2020-2-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 10:02:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwak.com/posts/brackeys-game-jam-2020-2-day-1/</guid>
      <description>2020-08-01 0800H EDT Woke up and the jam has been going on for 2 hours already. The theme is &amp;ldquo;REWIND&amp;rdquo;. Time for coffee and to noodle on some ideas for the game.
2020-08-01 1000H EDT I have a couple of ideas around the theme. In no particular order:
 A maze game where you can only go backwards by a &amp;ldquo;REWIND&amp;rdquo;. You only get so many rewinds per level. A time traveler game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>